funkruti.com 2010-02-02

# 

**Publication Date: 02nd January 2009  
**

We has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: www.FunKruti.com

 **Right to Change Policy**  
As FunKruti is constantly innovating and enhancing the type of services it provides to its users, this Privacy Statement will also continue to change to match the services and features we make available. As such, we reserve the right to change this statement to match the services we provide. If we make any material change to this statement, we will change the date at the top of this statement to reflect the effective date of the change. When you visit our site or use our services and site features, we encourage you to check the date of this Privacy Statement to ensure you are aware of any updates. However, regardless of how this Privacy Statement may change or evolve over time, FunKruti will not collect or maintain your private and personally identifiable information without your consent. Further, if you consent to give us your personal information, we will keep it confidential and will not sell, license or disclose your personal information to any third party without your consent, unless we are compelled to do so under the law or to comply with court order.

 **Types of Information We Collect**  
Generally, you are free to browse the FunKruti site without submitting any personal information. We do not collect any of your personal information (such as a name, address or email address) when you visit the FunKruti, unless you register or have registered to use our message boards, or otherwise agree to submit to us such information.

 **Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site.

 **Password Encryption**  
Please note that registration in our message boards require that you specify a password for your use. This password is then encrypted by our forums automatically, which means that the staff of FunKruti does not have access or knowledge of what your exact password is. This gives you ample security in case you are using the same password repeatedly in other sites (which is strongly discouraged).

 **What are Cookies? Why do we use them?**  
FunKruti uses browser cookies to facilitate your experience with our services and site features. These cookies are small sections of code that our server sends to your browser which it can then store on your hard drive. If you choose to accept these cookies, they enable us to recognize that your browser has previously visited and used our site and its services and, based on your browser's previous visits, assist us with tailoring the information andcontent you will receive. An example of the customization allowed by the use of such cookies is to retain your username and password as part of the FunKruti forums on our site so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit. These cookies do not collect, store or maintain your private, personally identifiable information. You do not have to accept these cookies to visit or use the FunKruti site or our forums, and you can choose to refuse our cookie, delete our cookie from your hard drive or turn off the FunKruti cookie at any time by updating your user profile preferences.

 **Information on Advertisers/Sponsors**  
We display unobtrusive ads or buttons on our site from outside advertising companies. These ads or buttons may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

Google Adsense Policy

[DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx): 

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. FunKruti is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

 **Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, message boards, and/or other news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

 **Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.

 **Postings on Message Boards**  
It is important for you to remain aware that when you provide personal information (e.g., last name, address, phone number) in a posting on any message board, that information is available to any other person or user having access and use of that message board, and may be used by someone in a manner unintended by you. For that reason, we discourage you from offering any personally identifying information within a posting to any message board.

 **Data Quality/Access**  
This site gives users the option of changing and modifying information previously provided. Visit your profile to change information.

 **Your Consent to this Policy**  
By using our Site, you agree to this Policy. This document supersedes any prior communication on this topic and reflects the entire and exclusive Privacy Policy for this Site. We may change our Policy by posting a new version of it on our Site at any time.

 **Legal Stuff**  
We are posting this Policy to be a good web citizen. This site operates in good faith, but on an AS-IS, AS-AVAILABLE BASIS. Any warranties of accuracy, quality, title, fitness or merchantibility are disclaimed. We are not liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damages. We are not liable for events beyond our direct control.

 **Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can reach us through email - [info@FunKruti.com](mailto:info@FunKruti.com)
